<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyMentalHealthChallenge</string>

    <string name="day1">Day 1 : Spend time alone</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2 : Dabble in a hobby</string>
    <string name="day3">Day 3 : Take 3 hours to unplug from technology</string>
    <string name="day4">Day 4 : Fix anything that bugs you</string>
    <string name="day5">Day 5 : Meditate for 5 minutes</string>
    <string name="day6">Day 6 : Guided journal prompts for 15 minutes</string>
    <string name="day7">Day 7 : Brain dump for 15 minutes</string>
    <string name="day8">Day 8 : Digital detox – delete, unsubscribe</string>
    <string name="day9">Day 9 : Positive affirmations throughout the day</string>
    <string name="day10">Day 10 : Schedule a friend date</string>
    <string name="day11">Day 11 : Reflect on your struggles and strengths</string>
    <string name="day12">Day 12 : Go to bed 30 minutes earlier</string>
    <string name="day13">Day 13 : Do an endorphin boosting activity</string>
    <string name="day14">Day 14 : Organize your closet</string>
    <string name="day15">Day 15 : Ask for help when you could use it</string>
    <string name="day16">Day 16 : Avoid complaining for the day</string>
    <string name="day17">Day 17 : Journal gratitudes for 10 minutes</string>
    <string name="day18">Day 18 : Do a relaxing activity</string>
    <string name="day19">Day 19 : Do something for yourself without guilt</string>
    <string name="day20">Day 20 : Genuinely compliment yourself</string>
    <string name="day21">Day 21 : Make a list of your accomplishments</string>
    <string name="day22">Day 22 : Read about a topic you enjoy</string>
    <string name="day23">Day 23 : Do something that lets you turn your brain off</string>
    <string name="day24">Day 24 : Practice saying no</string>
    <string name="day25">Day 25 : Do something outside your comfort zone</string>
    <string name="day26">Day 26 : Open up about something on your mind</string>
    <string name="day27">Day 27 : Set yourself up for therapy</string>
    <string name="day28">Day 28 : Reflect on the month</string>
    <string name="day29">Day 29 : Choose 3 habits from this challenge to keep</string>
    <string name="day30">Day 30 : Celebrate your progress</string>

    <string name="descDay1">Spend time alone and reflect on your thoughts and emotions[^1^][1]. This can help you understand your feelings better and improve your emotional intelligence.</string>
    <string name="descDay2">Engage in a hobby that brings you joy or find a new one[^2^][2]. This can be a great stress reliever and can also help you discover new passions.</string>
    <string name="descDay3">Take a 3-hour break from technology and social media. This can help reduce screen time and improve your mental health.</string>
    <string name="descDay4">Fix anything that bothers you in your environment. This can help create a more positive and productive space.</string>
    <string name="descDay5">Meditate for 5 minutes using a guided app or breathing exercises. This can help reduce stress and improve mindfulness.</string>
    <string name="descDay6">Journal about your mental health using a prompt or a brain dump. This can help you understand your feelings and emotions better.</string>
    <string name="descDay7">Do a digital detox by deleting, unsubscribing, and tidying up your online accounts. This can help reduce digital clutter and improve your online experience.</string>
    <string name="descDay8">Repeat positive affirmations to yourself throughout the day[^3^][3]. This can help improve your self-esteem and positivity.</string>
    <string name="descDay9">Catch up with a friend by calling or texting them. This can help strengthen your relationships and improve your social health.</string>
    <string name="descDay10">Make a list of 5 strengths and 5 struggles you have and reflect on them[^4^][4]. This can help you understand yourself better and improve your self-awareness.</string>
    <string name="descDay11">Go to bed 30 minutes earlier than usual. This can help improve your sleep quality and overall health.</string>
    <string name="descDay12">Do something that releases endorphins, such as laughing, exercising, or eating. This can help improve your mood and overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="descDay13">Declutter your closet and organize your clothes. This can help reduce physical clutter and improve your organization skills.</string>
    <string name="descDay14">Ask for help when you could use it and prepare for how to do it. This can help improve your problem-solving skills and resilience.</string>
    <string name="descDay15">Make a conscious effort not to complain for the whole day[^5^][5]. This can help improve your positivity and overall mood.</string>
    <string name="descDay16">Journal about what you are grateful for and why[^6^][6]. This can help improve your gratitude and overall happiness.</string>
    <string name="descDay17">Choose at least one relaxing activity that makes you feel calm and zen[^7^][7]. This can help reduce stress and improve your relaxation skills.</string>
    <string name="descDay18">Do something nice for yourself without feeling guilty[^8^][8]. This can help improve your self-care and overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="descDay19">Give yourself a genuine compliment and believe it[^9^][9]. This can help improve your self-esteem and overall self-image.</string>
    <string name="descDay20">Write down a list of your accomplishments and celebrate them. This can help improve your self-confidence and overall self-worth.</string>
    <string name="descDay21">Learn something new that interests you, whether it\'s educational or random. This can help improve your knowledge and overall intellectual health.</string>
    <string name="descDay22">Do something that lets you turn your brain off and isn\'t stimulating. This can help improve your relaxation and overall mental health.</string>
    <string name="descDay23">Practice saying no when you need to and set healthy boundaries[^10^][10]. This can help improve your assertiveness and overall interpersonal skills.</string>
    <string name="descDay24">Go outside your comfort zone and do something that challenges you. This can help improve your courage and overall personal growth.</string>
    <string name="descDay25">Vent to someone or on social media about something that bothers you. This can help improve your emotional expression and overall mental health.</string>
    <string name="descDay26">Try online therapy or continue with your current therapy sessions. This can help improve your mental health and overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="descDay27">Reflect on how the challenge has gone and what improvements you\'ve noticed. This can help improve your self-reflection and overall self-awareness.</string>
    <string name="descDay28">Choose 3 of your favorite activities from the challenge to keep as regular habits. This can help improve your routine and overall lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="descDay29">Create a self-care plan that\'s personalized to you and your needs[^11^][11]. This can help improve your self-care and overall well-being.</string>
    <string name="descDay30">Share your experience with the challenge and encourage others to try it. This can help improve your communication skills and overall social health.</string>
</resources>
